[Music]
many unique features in this product uh
uh first of all this is a completely
modular in nature the product which we
have designed the name of the product is
elev uh the key addons the features
which we have introduced in this product
one is uh infinite care cover which is
given to the customers in this cover we
are introducing industry first feature
which is in the lifetime of the policy
customer can request and Avail claim of
any unlimited amount but it can be
claimed only once throughout the
lifetime of the policy this cover today
is not available in the industry itself
so this is a very unique cover which is
there and for the very first time IC is
really proud to have introduced for the
larger audience of
uh see today largely whatever products
are available in the market uh maximum
uh have a capping they tell you that
today the some insured can be 5 lakh or
10 lakh or 20 lakh or 30 lakh or 50 lakh
something of that sort uh typically any
any good customer would always want to
have a security a peace of mind that
what if my claim amount or if I want to
uh get a higher some insured to to to
solve that for problem what we have done
is we have introduced unlimited some
insured option in our new product
Elevate here customer can has a option
to choose from 5 lakhs some insurance to
up till unlimited times C some insurance
whatever he wants to choose from so this
is for the very first time uh and it's a
interestly leading uh feature which we
have introduced in our as you know we
are a we are we are a big population in
our country uh we are number one
population wise our country right now
has one out of three people are
suffering from diabetes and it is
growing day by day uh as that population
is growing and then there are so many uh
ailments which are coming there are so
many uh things which are people are
suffering from all those customers today
typically in any health insurance plans
has to wait for a certain time to get
those ailments covered in the normal
policy by virtue of elevate by virtue of
jump start add-on which we have given in
our product this waiting period is now
getting reduced to 31 days so that is
the unique feature which is again there
in our product
elate it provide a very comprehensive
coverage it is completely modular it is
very much
personalized uh it has so many options
for any customer to optain he can select
whatever he wants uh from a variety of
add-on functions which are most most of
them are best in class uh new to the
industry or or best in the industry so
it is given a complete a complete peace
of mind and more importantly a wide
range of options to choose from jump
start feature which is there which we
call jump start it gives the flexibility
of to customer to start to get their PDS
covered from very 31st day so that is a
feature that is a thing which which is
getting covered from 31st day all PDS
will get covered in this weend the
Elevate product is an industry first as
VI also mentioned none of the companies
have been offering such an unlimited
cover to any uh you know policy holder
so that is why I feels that it is a very
unique positioning of the you know in
the health insurance industry it's a
revolutionary product for the health
insurance industry and it will benefit
the
customer so the base plan which is there
a customer can choose a b plan and on
top of that he can add any options which
he wants rather than taking a customized
rather than taking a standard on product
which is available in the market here he
can customize according to his needs or
his future requirements that is why it's
a different product
compan thank you than you yes I think we
are really very excited because this is
the first product in the market which is
bagged or enabled by AI what we have
done since this product gives power to
to customer to choose from variety of
options which are available uh at times
we think that mean there has to be some
recommendation which should go from our
side to the customer what he should
buy so what we have done is we have
basis the personas of customer we have
we have uh integrated our systems their
algorithms which are made and hence in
our systems for any customer we are
recommending a plan with some add-ons
which he should be buying basis our
recommendation tool basis his demography
basis his uh other personas which are we
are capturing at the time of sale so in
a way we are trying to help customer out
to tell him that hey look these are the
add-ons you should buy but this is just
a recommendation still customer has full
choice to add or delete whatever he
wants last question is like what makes
the power booster add on a signific
addition to the
it is very unique feature in the market
because power booster is one feature
which gives a bonus of 100% year on year
typically in our Market uh the bonus
which is given is to the tune of 2x 4X
5x or at in sometimes up till 10x
there's a limitation to that in our
product we have said irrespective of
claim your bonus will keep on increasing
year on year up to unlimited time so it
will keep on growing until you keep on
renewing the policy so as simple as that
and again this is industry first feature
which we have launched in
our thank you thank you very much